I really wish folks would stop playing in my face.
I was asked to speak at a black graduation.
I said I would do it for free.
Then they just canceled it, saying that they will no longer be able to have me at the graduation due to budgetary issues.
Here's what I want from all of us.
Honesty.
You know, that's really what is allowing for so much of what's happening in the world to happen.
It's because honesty is not a value that's valued.
Transparency.
There's all of this fake politeness that actually is not progression based at all.
And I take it personal, actually.
No, I don't take anything personal.
But I do take it as an affront when folks just don't keep it a buck.
So, anywho.
Quit playing in folks' faces.